Jessie Lloyd O'Connor Papers, 1850-1988
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATION FILES 1918-1988
  - International Registry of World Citizens1963, 1970, undated (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - International Society for Socialist Studies1958-60, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - International Workers Order1941-42, undated (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - I1939-79, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Jane Addams Centennial Committee1959-60, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Jane Addams Peace Association1932, 1959-88, undated (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Jeannette Rankin Brigade1967-68, undated (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science1954-55 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Joe Hill House of Hospitality and St. Joseph's Refuge (Box 117)
    [see SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE--Hennacy, Ammon; and SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES--Hennacy, Ammon ]
  - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee
    - Correspondence1942-45 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Printed material1942-48, undated (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Keep America Out of War Congress1939-41, undated (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Kentucky Miners Relief Committee (Box 117)
    [see SERIES III. WRITINGS-Federated Press-Harlan, KY]
  - Koinonia1957-81, undated (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - J-K1950-77, undated (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Labor Research Association (Box 117)
    [see SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Hutchins, Grace]
  - Labor's Non-Partisan League of Cook County/Illinois1938-40, undated (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Latin American Research Bureau1951-54 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Law Students Council1973-74 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee1966-70 (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - League for Industrial Democracy1924-68 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - League for Mutual Aid1938-54, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - League for Social Justice1932-35, undated (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - League of Women Shoppers
    - Constitutionundated (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence1937-45,undated (Box 118, Folder 5-6)
    - Financial and fundraising1937-38, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Formsundated (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Lists of members and affiliates1937-38, undated (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Meeting materials1937-43, undated (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters and reports1937-45, undated (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Notesundated (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Pamphlets and flyers1937-43, undated (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Press releases and clippings1937-38, 1972, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - League of Women Voters
    - National printed material1934-51, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Illinois branches1938-45, undated (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts branches1949-52, undated (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, Texas1935-69 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Speech/statement and notes by JLOundated (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Liaison Committee to Women's Peace Groups1966-68 (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Liberal Citizens of Massachusetts1953-62 (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Liberation1957-70 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE Friends and associates-Muste, A.J.]
  - Lucy Parsons Collective Film Project1985-86 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - L1954-83 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Marian Rubins Davis Scholarship Fund
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Davis, Horace and Marian; and Davis, Natalie Zemon and Chandler Davis; and SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES-Davis, Marian Rubins]
    - General1961-83, undated (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence1962-86 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Meeting materials1962-86 (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts General Hospital1961-80, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Medgar Evers Fund1969-73, undated (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute1974-88 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Methodist Federation for Social Service/Social Action
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Ball, Lee and Maria]
    - Correspondence1941-62 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Social Questions Bulletin1934-77 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Printed material1937-73, undated (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council of Chicago
    - Correspondence1940-66 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Reports1943-45, 1949, 1950, 1953 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Tomorrow's Chicago1947, 1954-55, 1961, 1965 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Notes1940-41, undated (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Printed material and two photos1934-65, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Migrant Children's Fund1958-63 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Minority of One1961, 1963-65 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Minute Women for Peace1950-53, undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Mobilization for Survival1977-86, undated (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Mutual Real Estate Investment Trust1966-68, undated (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - M1944-80, undated (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - The Nation1932, 1949-80 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - National Advisory Committee on Farm Labor1963-64 (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - National Alliance Against Racist and Political Repression1973-74, undated (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - National Anti-Klan Network1980-81 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People
    - Correspondence1948, 1960, 1963 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - "Committee of 100" 1957-68 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Printed material1954-73, undated (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - National Child Labor Committee
    - The American Child1949-52 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Printed material1939, 1942, 1949-59, undated (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - National Citizens Committee for Broadcasting1970, undated (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - National Citizens Political Action Committee1953-70, 1987 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation/National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE -Wilkinson, Jean, Frank, and Donna]
    - Correspondence and notes1964-88 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Meeting minutes1962-64, 1968 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Financial material1963-71 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters1964, 1968, 1971 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Printed material1960-83, undated (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - New York Branch1961-64, undated (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Other branches (Massachusetts, Northwest Committee, Washington Area Committee, Southern California, Northern California, New England, Midwest Region)1962-71 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - National Committee for an Effective Congress1952-72, undated (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - National Committee for the Repeal of the McCarran Act1962-65, undated (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools1957, undated (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - National Committee for the Control of Radiation Hazards1960-61, undated (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - National Committee on the Education of Migrant Children1964, 1968-70, undated (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 121)
    [see National Committee to Abolish Repressive Legislation]
  - National Committee to Abolish the Poll Tax1942-44, undated (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - National Committee to Aid Victims of German Fascism1933-34, undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
    [see also SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES--Eisler, Hans]
  - National Committee to Re-open the Rosenberg Case1953, 1974, undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - National Committee to Secure Justice for Morton Sobell in the Rosenberg Case/Chicago Sobell Committee1953-67, undated (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - National Committee to Stop Environment Pollution1970-71, undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - National Committee to Win Amnesty for the Smith Act Victims1954, undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - National Community Funds/Funding Exchange1982-85, undated (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - National Conference for New Politics1966-68, undated (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - National Consumers League1939-53, undated (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - National Council Against Conscription
    - General1948-55, undated (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Conscription News1948-53 (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - National Council for American-Soviet Friendship
    - General1945-74, undated (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Report on American Soviet Relations1945-46 (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - National Council of Negro Women1968-72 (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - National Council to Repeal the Draft1970-73 (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee1970-86 (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - National Emergency Conference1939 (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - National Emergency Conference for Democratic Rights1940 (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - National Federation for Constitutional Liberties
    - General1940-45, undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Action Letter1941-45 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - National Forum Foundation
    - Correspondence1944-63 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Printed material1952-59, undated (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - National Guardian
    - Correspondence1946-55, undated (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Printed material1949-65, undated (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - National Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace1967 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - National Lawyers Guild1939, 1960-74 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - National Peace Academy Campaign1977-78 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - National Public Housing Conference1944-45 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - National Sharecroppers1950-71, undated (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - National Social Center1938 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - National Unemployment League1937-38, undated (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - National Woman's Party
    - General1961-77, undated (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence1935, 1964-83, undated (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Publications1937-74 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Publicity1965-78, undated (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Supporters' lists and statements1945-72, undated (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - National Women's Appeal for the Rights of Foreign Born Americans (Box 123)
  - Native American Solidarity Committee1975-77 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - New Christian (Box 124)
    [see SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE--Friends and associates-Leslie, Kenneth]
  - New Democratic Coalition of Rhode Island1969-71, undated (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - New England Citizens Concerned for Peace1950-54 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - New England Folk Festival Association1979-80 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - New York Citizens' Committee for a Peoples' World Convention (Box 124)
    [see SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Fenner, Frances]
  - New York Committee to Free Angela Davis (Box 124)
    [see SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES-Davis, Angela]
  - Non-Violent Action against Nuclear Weapons1957-58 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - N1932-87 (Box 124, Folder 6-7)
  - Oil Workers International Union1944-48, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma Committee for the Defense of Political Prisoners1940-41 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Operation Freedom1961-1974, undated (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - O1954-79, undated (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Pacem in Terris1963-72 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Partners in Housing1972-83 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Pax1963-72, undated (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Peace and Freedom Party1966-83, undated (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Peace Concern1962-64, undated (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Peace Museum1980-82 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Peacemakers1951-65 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Peaceways1961-69 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania Civil Liberties Committee (Box 125)
    [see SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Harper, Allan G., Kathleen, and Ernest]
  - Peoples Artists1947-56 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Hays, Lee]
  - People's Institute of Applied Religion
    - History1944-74, undated (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence1941-46, undated (Box 125, Folder 5)
      [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Foth, Annette E.]
    - Memoranda1945-46 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Programs1941-46, undated (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Publications1943-47, undated (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Publicity1942-51, undated (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - People's Legislative Committee1946-50, undated (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Peoples Lobby
    - Correspondence1929-70, undated (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters1934-70 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Programs1937-48 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Publicity1943-46, undated (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Reports1941-50 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Speeches1944-46 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - People's Party1971-77 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - People's Progressive Party1965-88 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - People's Progressive Party of New Guinea1960-67 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - People's Songs, Inc. (Box 125)
    [see SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES--Music]
  - People's World Constitutional Convention1950-58, undated (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility1980-82 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Pittsburgh Civil Liberties Committee1933-34, 1954, undated (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Planned Parenthood Federation of Americacirca 1940-81, undated (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Political Action for Peace1960 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Political Rights Defense Fundundated (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Post War World Council1940s-67 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Powell-Schuman Defense Committee1956-59 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Progressive Party
    [see also SERIES III. WRITINGS--Articles and essays-Alphabetical by subject- Wallace, Henry; and SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES-Political campaigns]
    - National
      - Correspondence1943-55 (Box 126, Folder 8)
      - Conferences1948-54 (Box 126, Folder 9)
      - Memoranda1952-55, undated (Box 126, Folder 10)
      - Promotional material1948-54, undated (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - Newsletters1948-55 (Box 126, Folder 12)
      - Press releases1952-54 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - Reports1952-54, undated (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - Speeches and broadcasts1952-54 (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - Statements and policies1948-54 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Affiliates
      - California1953-55 (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - Chicago1953 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - District of Columbia1953-54 (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - Maryland1953-54, undated (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Massachusetts: General and correspondence1948-53, undated (Box 127, Folder 6-7)
        - Newsletters1948-53 (Box 127, Folder 8)
        - Publicity1948-55, undated (Box 127, Folder 9)
        - Testimonials1948-58, undated (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - New Jersey
        - Newsletter1953-54 (Box 127, Folder 11)
        - Publicity1953-57, undated (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - Ohio1953-55, undated (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - Philadelphia1952-55 (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - Rhode Island1948, 1952, undated (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - Texas1948 (Box 127, Folder 16)
      - Vermont1952 (Box 127, Folder 17)
      - Wisconsin1953-54 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Wallace for President Clubs1948-49 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Women for Wallace1948, 1959 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - Promoting Enduring Peacecirca 1949-68, undated (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - The Protestant1942-52, undated (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - P1934-86, undated (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - Radical Education Project1966-69 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Rassemblement Universel pour la Paix1938 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Religious Freedom Committee1960-64 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Resist1968-80, undated (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Rhode Island Maternal Health Association1952-63, undated (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Rhode Island Workers Association1978, undated (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Rhode Islanders for Safe Powerundated (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Russia War Relief1942-44, undated (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - R1938-84 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Sakonnet World Federalist meetingcirca 1960-64 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - SANE (National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy)
    - Correspondence1958-72, undated (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Printed material1957-75, undated (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Policies1957-67 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Publications1961-80, undated (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Publicity1957-67, undated (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Scholarship, Education, and Defense Fund for Social Equality1967-70, undated (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - School of Youth for Social Science1968-circa 1970, undated (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Scottsboro Hernden Defense Fundcirca 1938 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    [see also International Labor Defense]
  - Slate1961-62 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Socialist Labor Party1952-79 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - Socialist Party
    - Newsletterscirca 1930, 1961-81 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Discussion bulletins1974 (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Publicity1940-75, undated (Box 128, Folder 23)
  - Socialist Workers Campaign Committee1968 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Society of Separationists1966 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Songs of the American People (Box 129)
    [see SERIES V. SUBJECTS FILES--Music]
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference1963-74 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund
    [see also Southern Conference for Human Welfare; SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE--Braden, Anne and Carl, and Goldberg, Ruth; and SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES--Braden, Anne and Carl]
    - Correspondence and fundraising appeals1948-74 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Leaflets and pamphlets1948-74 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda1960-74 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters1945-76 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Publications1954-circa 1970 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Publicity1953-68 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - 1974 Split1973-74 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Southern Conference for Human Welfare1940-47, undated (Box 129, Folder 11)
    [see also Southern Conference Educational Fund]
  - Southern Institute for Propaganda and Organizing1974 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Southern Organizing Committee for Social and Economic Justice1978-88, undated (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Southern Poverty Law Center1971-74, 1970s (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Southern Summer School for Workers1939-43 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Spanish Refugee Aid, Inc.1956-70 (Box 129, Folder 16)
  - Sphere1958-59 (Box 129, Folder 17)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee1937 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Student Non-violent Coordinating Committee1962-68 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - S1938-84, undated (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - T.U.S. Press1952-53 (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Textile Workers of America1946-47 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Thomas A. Dooley Foundation1965 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Toward World Democracy1955-62 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Town Meeting Committee1950 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Turn Toward Peace1960-66, 1960s (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Tuskegee Institute1931-32 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - T1938-82, undated (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Unified Buddhist Church of Vietnam1970-72 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Union for Democratic Action1942-45 (Box 130, Folder 13)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists1970s (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Unitarian Church
    - Correspondence and notes1947-87 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Church newsletters1945-75 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Orders of Service and Programs1956-67, undated (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Sermons1946-65, undated (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Unitarian-Universalist Service Committee1944-87 (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - United Automobile Workers1942-62 (Box 130, Folder 20)
  - United Conference Against the High Cost of Living1937-43 (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - United Congregational Church (Little Compton, RI)circa 1945-83 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - United Electrical Workers' Union1949-57, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - United Farm Workers1974-76 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - United Nations Association1945, 1973, 1976 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - United Negro College Fund1970, 1972 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America1939-41 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - United Packinghouse Workers of America1947-48 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Committee Against Militarization1952-64 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Committee for Cooperation with the Japan Council Against A & H Bombs1961-62 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Committee for Democracy in Greecec.1968-1970 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - United States Committee for Justice to Latin American Political Prisoners1973 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Peace Council1979 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - United World Federalists
    - Correspondence1947-67 (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda1947-67 (Box 131, Folder 14)
    - Fundraising appeals1950-68, 1960s (Box 131, Folder 15)
    - Publicity: newspaper clippings and reprints1958-67 (Box 131, Folder 16)
    - Addresses and remarks1947-63 (Box 131, Folder 17)
    - Lists1946-57, 1950s, 1960s (Box 131, Folder 18)
    - Events: agendas and invitations1962-68, 1960s (Box 131, Folder 19)
    - Policies and statements1947-64, undated (Box 131, Folder 20)
    - Leaflets1957-70, undated (Box 131, Folder 21)
    - Pamphlets1946-65 (Box 131, Folder 22)
    - Newsletters1945-67 (Box 131, Folder 23)
    - Reports1954-66, 1960s (Box 131, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous1958-1970 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - United World Federalists of Chicago1958-65, undated (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - United World Federalists of New England1953-65 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - University of British Columbia1958-60 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - U1937-83, undated (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade1938, 1958-64, undated (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War1972-74 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Voice of Women
    - Newsletters1962-63 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Publicity: bulletins, leaflets, and statements1960-68 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Conferences:
      - 1962: correspondence, publicity, reports, notes, typescripts, and programs (Box 132, Folder 8)
      - 1966: list and reprint, 1966 (Box 132, Folder 9)
      - 1967: correspondence, lists, agenda, notes, programs, and summary (Box 132, Folder 10)
      - 1969: correspondence (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - V1938, 1966, undated (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - W.A.G.E.1981-83 (Box 132, Folder 13)
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE--Friends and associates--Matthews, Doug, and Shelton, Henry]
  - War/Peace Report1964-65, undated (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - War Resisters League
    - Correspondence1965-73, 1980 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    - Conference announcements1969-80, undated (Box 132, Folder 16)
    - Fundraising appeals1959-79 (Box 132, Folder 17)
    - Newsletters1960-75 (Box 132, Folder 18)
    - Promotional material1941-1980s (Box 132, Folder 19)
    - Reports1964-80 (Box 132, Folder 20)
    - Statements1961-80s (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Warren's Point Association1982-87 (Box 132, Folder 22)
  - Willard Uphaus Committee1955-60 (Box 132, Folder 23)
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE--Friends and associates--Uphaus, Ola and Willard]
  - Woman's City Club of Chicago1940-49 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Women For a Non-Nuclear Future1980-88, undated (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Women For Peace1961-74, undated (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Women Investors in America1935-36, undated (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Women Strike for Peace
    - Correspondence and clippings1962-72 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Printed material1961-68, undated (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Flyers, broadsides, and pamphlets1963-67, undated (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Mother's Lobby1963 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - National Conferences1962-66 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Women's Bureau, Department of Labor1937-39, undated (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Women's Campaign Fund1977-80 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Women's International League For Peace and Freedom
    [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates--Carner, Lucy; Fowler, Eleanor; Friedman, Dorothy; Gilbert, Louise; Mills, Doris; and Shelley, Rebecca]
    - Chicago Branches1944-49, 1970, undated (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence1931-83, undated (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Notes and writings1955-56 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Providence Branch1950-66 (Box 133, Folder 15)
      [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE--Friends and associates--Fichter, Evelyn]
    - Miscellaneous and printed material1928-81, undated (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Women's Joint Committee On Adequate Housing1941-45 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - Women's Liberation Union of Rhode Island1977-84, undated (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Women's Trade Union League of Chicago1937-49 (Box 134, Folder 1)